{"experimentVersion":"micro_debug","participantID":"test","participantAge":"t","participantGender":2,"confirmationCode":"0102361","participantFeedback":"","totalTrials":14,"dataRecordFrequency":0.03999999910593033,"restbreakDuration":5.0,"getReadyDuration":5.0,"trialList":[0,1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10,11,12,13],"allTrialData":[{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[0],"mapName":"Persistent","trialAnswer":"","trialQuestion":"","trialStimulus":"","trialPossibleAnswers":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.0,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":0.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"pausePriorFeedbackTime":0.30000001192092898,"feedbackFlashDuration":1.2000000476837159,"trialScore":0.0,"maxResponseTime":5.0,"responseTime":[0.0],"responseChoice":[""],"choiceCorrect":[false],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[false],"FLAG_trialError":[false]},{"trialNumber":1,"trialListIndex":[1],"mapName":"InformationScreen","trialAnswer":"","trialQuestion":"","trialStimulus":"","trialPossibleAnswers":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.0,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":0.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"pausePriorFeedbackTime":0.30000001192092898,"feedbackFlashDuration":1.2000000476837159,"trialScore":0.0,"maxResponseTime":5.0,"responseTime":[0.0],"responseChoice":[""],"choiceCorrect":[false],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[false],"FLAG_trialError":[false]},{"trialNumber":2,"trialListIndex":[2],"mapName":"BeforeStartingScreen","trialAnswer":"","trialQuestion":"","trialStimulus":"","trialPossibleAnswers":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.0,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":0.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"pausePriorFeedbackTime":0.30000001192092898,"feedbackFlashDuration":1.2000000476837159,"trialScore":0.0,"maxResponseTime":5.0,"responseTime":[0.0],"responseChoice":[""],"choiceCorrect":[false],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[false],"FLAG_trialError":[false]},{"trialNumber":3,"trialListIndex":[3],"mapName":"ConsentScreen","trialAnswer":"","trialQuestion":"","trialStimulus":"","trialPossibleAnswers":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.0,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":0.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"pausePriorFeedbackTime":0.30000001192092898,"feedbackFlashDuration":1.2000000476837159,"trialScore":0.0,"maxResponseTime":5.0,"responseTime":[0.0],"responseChoice":[""],"choiceCorrect":[false],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[false],"FLAG_trialError":[false]},{"trialNumber":4,"trialListIndex":[4],"mapName":"StartScreen","trialAnswer":"","trialQuestion":"","trialStimulus":"","trialPossibleAnswers":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.0,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":0.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"pausePriorFeedbackTime":0.30000001192092898,"feedbackFlashDuration":1.2000000476837159,"trialScore":0.0,"maxResponseTime":5.0,"responseTime":[0.0],"responseChoice":[""],"choiceCorrect":[false],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[false],"FLAG_trialError":[false]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"InstructionsScreen","trialAnswer":"","trialQuestion":"","trialStimulus":"","trialPossibleAnswers":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.0,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":0.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"pausePriorFeedbackTime":0.30000001192092898,"feedbackFlashDuration":1.2000000476837159,"trialScore":0.0,"maxResponseTime":5.0,"responseTime":[],"responseChoice":[],"choiceCorrect":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"Practice","trialAnswer":"Yes!","trialQuestion":"Is this game fun and all things good?","trialStimulus":"questionIcon","trialPossibleAnswers":["Na it sucks","It's ok, I guess","Yes!"],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.0,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":0.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"pausePriorFeedbackTime":0.30000001192092898,"feedbackFlashDuration":1.2000000476837159,"trialScore":0.0,"maxResponseTime":5.0,"responseTime":[],"responseChoice":[],"choiceCorrect":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"GetReady","trialAnswer":"","trialQuestion":"","trialStimulus":"","trialPossibleAnswers":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.0,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":0.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"pausePriorFeedbackTime":0.30000001192092898,"feedbackFlashDuration":1.2000000476837159,"trialScore":0.0,"maxResponseTime":5.0,"responseTime":[],"responseChoice":[],"choiceCorrect":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"MainTrial","trialAnswer":"Yes!","trialQuestion":"Is this game fun and all things good?","trialStimulus":"questionIcon","trialPossibleAnswers":["Na it sucks","It's ok, I guess","Yes!"],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.0,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":0.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"pausePriorFeedbackTime":0.30000001192092898,"feedbackFlashDuration":1.2000000476837159,"trialScore":0.0,"maxResponseTime":5.0,"responseTime":[],"responseChoice":[],"choiceCorrect":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"MainTrial","trialAnswer":"No","trialQuestion":"Is this a bird?","trialStimulus":"icecream","trialPossibleAnswers":["Yes","No"],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.0,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":0.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"pausePriorFeedbackTime":0.30000001192092898,"feedbackFlashDuration":1.2000000476837159,"trialScore":0.0,"maxResponseTime":5.0,"responseTime":[],"responseChoice":[],"choiceCorrect":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"MainTrial","trialAnswer":"I think I am, B2","trialQuestion":"Are you thinking what I'm thinking, B1?","trialStimulus":"banana","trialPossibleAnswers":["No","I think I am, B2"],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.0,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":0.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"pausePriorFeedbackTime":0.30000001192092898,"feedbackFlashDuration":1.2000000476837159,"trialScore":0.0,"maxResponseTime":5.0,"responseTime":[],"responseChoice":[],"choiceCorrect":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"MainTrial","trialAnswer":"Yes","trialQuestion":"Is this a cheese?","trialStimulus":"cheese","trialPossibleAnswers":["Yes","No"],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.0,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":0.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"pausePriorFeedbackTime":0.30000001192092898,"feedbackFlashDuration":1.2000000476837159,"trialScore":0.0,"maxResponseTime":5.0,"responseTime":[],"responseChoice":[],"choiceCorrect":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"MainTrial","trialAnswer":": (","trialQuestion":"How many avocado-toasts does a house cost?","trialStimulus":"avocado","trialPossibleAnswers":["1","10","100","1000",": ("],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.0,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":0.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"pausePriorFeedbackTime":0.30000001192092898,"feedbackFlashDuration":1.2000000476837159,"trialScore":0.0,"maxResponseTime":5.0,"responseTime":[],"responseChoice":[],"choiceCorrect":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"Exit","trialAnswer":"","trialQuestion":"","trialStimulus":"","trialPossibleAnswers":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.0,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":0.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"pausePriorFeedbackTime":0.30000001192092898,"feedbackFlashDuration":1.2000000476837159,"trialScore":0.0,"maxResponseTime":5.0,"responseTime":[],"responseChoice":[],"choiceCorrect":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[]}]}